[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "Do you think personally think homosexuality is a sin?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "personally", "think", "homosexuality", "is", "a", "sin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "Nice try.", "answer_tokens": ["Nice", "try", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "That's a valid question, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "valid", "question", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "It's a valid question and my answer is: nice try.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "valid", "question", "and", "my", "answer", "is", ":", "nice", "try", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Are you harmless?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "harmless", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "I think I'm a pussycat.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "'m", "a", "pussycat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "It's fun, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "fun", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Great fun.", "answer_tokens": ["Great", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "-- provocative, my kind of girl, right?", "question_tokens": ["--", "provocative", ",", "my", "kind", "of", "girl", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "-- want power?", "question_tokens": ["--", "want", "power", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "No, of course, politicians seek power.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "of", "course", ",", "politicians", "seek", "power", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "But why is it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "why", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "What happened was it was like a three or four step process.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "happened", "was", "it", "was", "like", "a", "three", "or", "four", "step", "process", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Why didn't you do anything about it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "n't", "you", "do", "anything", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "He tried.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "tried", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Over eight years?", "question_tokens": ["Over", "eight", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNPS", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "CC", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "-- blame the Democrats for an eight year regime which does nothing about?", "question_tokens": ["--", "blame", "the", "Democrats", "for", "an", "eight", "year", "regime", "which", "does", "nothing", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "DT", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "The Democrats pushed this politically or rather financially suicidal loans on the banks, literally allowing unemployment benefits to be used as collateral.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "Democrats", "pushed", "this", "politically", "or", "rather", "financially", "suicidal", "loans", "on", "the", "banks", ",", "literally", "allowing", "unemployment", "benefits", "to", "be", "used", "as", "collateral", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Why didn't your team do something about it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "n't", "your", "team", "do", "something", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "They did.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "What do you think of the bankers now who were bailed out awarding themselves multi -- multi-million dollar bonuses?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "bankers", "now", "who", "were", "bailed", "out", "awarding", "themselves", "multi", "--", "multi-million", "dollar", "bonuses", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "I can't stand them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "stand", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "WP", ":"], "qSentId": 162, "question": "Why is your instinctive gut reaction to everything I say, even when I'm agreeing with you, why is it always to mention the Democrats?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "your", "instinctive", "gut", "reaction", "to", "everything", "I", "say", ",", "even", "when", "I", "'m", "agreeing", "with", "you", ",", "why", "is", "it", "always", "to", "mention", "the", "Democrats", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Well, technically what --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "technically", "what", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Are you like programmed like a robot?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "like", "programmed", "like", "a", "robot", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "No, what I'm saying --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "what", "I", "'m", "saying", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 220, "question": "-- where is the similar mob to Mussolini's and Hitler's in the modern democratic era?", "question_tokens": ["--", "where", "is", "the", "similar", "mob", "to", "Mussolini", "'s", "and", "Hitler", "'s", "in", "the", "modern", "democratic", "era", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "CC", "NNP", "POS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Well, I would say that there are a lot of similarities to the French Revolution --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "say", "that", "there", "are", "a", "lot", "of", "similarities", "to", "the", "French", "Revolution", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mussolini", "Hitler"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "The Tea Party?", "question_tokens": ["The", "Tea", "Party", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party", "Tea Party"]}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "WDT", ":", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", ":", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "The nearest thing to it in America?", "question_tokens": ["The", "nearest", "thing", "to", "it", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "No, they're much closer to the original Tea Party which -- and actually not as -- not as much of a rabble as the original Tea Party, which, as I point out, the Founding Fathers weren't wild about the original Tea Party, curiously enough, because they were so against mobs.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "they", "'re", "much", "closer", "to", "the", "original", "Tea", "Party", "which", "--", "and", "actually", "not", "as", "--", "not", "as", "much", "of", "a", "rabble", "as", "the", "original", "Tea", "Party", ",", "which", ",", "as", "I", "point", "out", ",", "the", "Founding", "Fathers", "were", "n't", "wild", "about", "the", "original", "Tea", "Party", ",", "curiously", "enough", ",", "because", "they", "were", "so", "against", "mobs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Oh, the current Tea Party?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "the", "current", "Tea", "Party", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Well, a lot -- a lot of them aren't the brightest of sparrows, are they?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "a", "lot", "--", "a", "lot", "of", "them", "are", "n't", "the", "brightest", "of", "sparrows", ",", "are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "They're smarter than any liberal.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "smarter", "than", "any", "liberal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Do you think so?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "so", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Do you really think that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "think", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Yes, I do and I --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "and", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ":", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "In your heart?", "question_tokens": ["In", "your", "heart", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "-- meet them and I speak to them and they get my jokes -- which already makes them smarter than the average liberal.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "meet", "them", "and", "I", "speak", "to", "them", "and", "they", "get", "my", "jokes", "--", "which", "already", "makes", "them", "smarter", "than", "the", "average", "liberal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "So that's why you like them, because of their smiles?", "question_tokens": ["So", "that", "'s", "why", "you", "like", "them", ",", "because", "of", "their", "smiles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Well, it makes them smarter than the average liberal.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "makes", "them", "smarter", "than", "the", "average", "liberal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 260, "question": "What do you think she's said that's inflammatory?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "she", "'s", "said", "that", "'s", "inflammatory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Putting crosshairs on people's heads --", "answer_tokens": ["Putting", "crosshairs", "on", "people", "'s", "heads", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Is that inflammatory?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "inflammatory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["P.R."]}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Every single time I ask you a question, rather than answer about Sarah Palin and crosshairs, you instinctively go, what about the Democrats?", "question_tokens": ["Every", "single", "time", "I", "ask", "you", "a", "question", ",", "rather", "than", "answer", "about", "Sarah", "Palin", "and", "crosshairs", ",", "you", "instinctively", "go", ",", "what", "about", "the", "Democrats", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "The P.R. is darling.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "P.R.", "is", "darling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Would you encourage them to carry on doing it?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "encourage", "them", "to", "carry", "on", "doing", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "How do you know?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "-- to shoot up a shopping mall.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "to", "shoot", "up", "a", "shopping", "mall", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "How do you know?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Because we know that he's out of his mind.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "we", "know", "that", "he", "'s", "out", "of", "his", "mind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "IN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Then what would you think?", "question_tokens": ["Then", "what", "would", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Well, what if I --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "if", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Do you still think that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "think", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Do you really?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Well, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "You probably know, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "probably", "know", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "I haven't the first idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "the", "first", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", ":", "RB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Do you think she should?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "she", "should", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "I wouldn't if I were in her shoes, not for president -- maybe senator or something.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "if", "I", "were", "in", "her", "shoes", ",", "not", "for", "president", "--", "maybe", "senator", "or", "something", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "Is she dangerous?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "dangerous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "No, she's fabulous.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "she", "'s", "fabulous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "You don't see any fault line in Sarah Palin?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "see", "any", "fault", "line", "in", "Sarah", "Palin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "No, I think she's terrific.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "she", "'s", "terrific", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Why -- if you see it as such a low down profession, why are you so obsessed with it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "--", "if", "you", "see", "it", "as", "such", "a", "low", "down", "profession", ",", "why", "are", "you", "so", "obsessed", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "And you sleep until noon, is this right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "sleep", "until", "noon", ",", "is", "this", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "That's a bit weird, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "bit", "weird", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "Well, that's when I get up early.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "when", "I", "get", "up", "early", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Will you stop the shameless plugs?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "stop", "the", "shameless", "plugs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "It's out today.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "out", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNPS", "CC", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Should he resign?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "he", "resign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "Yes, I mean, the -- this is the difference between, among many others, among Democrats and Republicans on this.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "the", "--", "this", "is", "the", "difference", "between", ",", "among", "many", "others", ",", "among", "Democrats", "and", "Republicans", "on", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP$", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 457, "question": "-- who is defending -- allow me to -- who's defending women?", "question_tokens": ["--", "who", "is", "defending", "--", "allow", "me", "to", "--", "who", "'s", "defending", "women", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", ":", "JJ", "PRP", "TO", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Well, last week, they're -- your network --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "last", "week", ",", "they", "'re", "--", "your", "network", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBZ", "VB", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Is he fabulous?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "fabulous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "What mobs do is create -- and I have a chapter on this.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "mobs", "do", "is", "create", "--", "and", "I", "have", "a", "chapter", "on", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Who attacked Breitbart?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "attacked", "Breitbart", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "You're joking.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "joking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Breitbart"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Who seriously, on mainstream media, attacked him?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "seriously", ",", "on", "mainstream", "media", ",", "attacked", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I was traveling all -- all week last week, just a copy out at the beginning.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "traveling", "all", "--", "all", "week", "last", "week", ",", "just", "a", "copy", "out", "at", "the", "beginning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "I mean, because there's not a massive onslaught, is it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "because", "there", "'s", "not", "a", "massive", "onslaught", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "No, basically the entire mainstream media.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "basically", "the", "entire", "mainstream", "media", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "RB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 531, "question": "-- ever calm down?", "question_tokens": ["--", "ever", "calm", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Now, you're taking this very long question which I'm trying to give an answer, which is so contradicting --", "answer_tokens": ["Now", ",", "you", "'re", "taking", "this", "very", "long", "question", "which", "I", "'m", "trying", "to", "give", "an", "answer", ",", "which", "is", "so", "contradicting", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Sanford"]}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "On Mr. Breitbart, is it not understandable people might be at least skeptical given his track record?", "question_tokens": ["On", "Mr.", "Breitbart", ",", "is", "it", "not", "understandable", "people", "might", "be", "at", "least", "skeptical", "given", "his", "track", "record", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "I don't know who exposed Mark Sanford.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "who", "exposed", "Mark", "Sanford", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Breitbart"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Why didn't the Republicans expose Arnold -- Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "n't", "the", "Republicans", "expose", "Arnold", "--", "Arnold", "Schwarzenegger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NNPS", "VBD", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Good.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["L.A."]}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "WRB", ",", "RB", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "VBG", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "question_tokens": ["Arnold", "Schwarzenegger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Nobody said why, damn that \"L.A. Times\" for exposing this, I don't believe it.", "answer_tokens": ["Nobody", "said", "why", ",", "damn", "that", "``", "L.A.", "Times", "''", "for", "exposing", "this", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "believe", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "-- what's he still doing there?", "question_tokens": ["--", "what", "'s", "he", "still", "doing", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "-- because he has to hold a press conference because the photos came out.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "because", "he", "has", "to", "hold", "a", "press", "conference", "because", "the", "photos", "came", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "WP", ":"], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Do you hallucinate the liberals, seriously?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "hallucinate", "the", "liberals", ",", "seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Do you hallucinate about someone who --", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "you", "hallucinate", "about", "someone", "who", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "-- clearly sees the world and you aren't grasping it, so you get angry and frustrated and attack that person?", "question_tokens": ["--", "clearly", "sees", "the", "world", "and", "you", "are", "n't", "grasping", "it", ",", "so", "you", "get", "angry", "and", "frustrated", "and", "attack", "that", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "I never get angry.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", "get", "angry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner", "Wolf Blitzer"]}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 611, "question": "OULTER: -- doing a story on hacking last week?", "question_tokens": ["OULTER", ":", "--", "doing", "a", "story", "on", "hacking", "last", "week", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", ":", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "Because Anthony Weiner said publicly in an interview with Wolf Blitzer, \"I was hacked.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "Anthony", "Weiner", "said", "publicly", "in", "an", "interview", "with", "Wolf", "Blitzer", ",", "``", "I", "was", "hacked", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "You're 50 in December, are you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "50", "in", "December", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Don't talk about either engagements, Social Security number, age or anything else.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "talk", "about", "either", "engagements", ",", "Social", "Security", "number", ",", "age", "or", "anything", "else", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["December"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "You have never deliberately put the wrong age on a document?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "never", "deliberately", "put", "the", "wrong", "age", "on", "a", "document", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "I don't answer questions about myself.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "answer", "questions", "about", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "How would you react?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "react", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "I would be fine with it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "be", "fine", "with", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Would you?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "I can't imagine being married.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "imagine", "being", "married", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "Do you wish you hadn't said it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "wish", "you", "had", "n't", "said", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "Do you feel that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "It was because something was happening that week.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "because", "something", "was", "happening", "that", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Maher", "Bill Maher", "Dick Cheney"]}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "You're still responsible for your words, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "still", "responsible", "for", "your", "words", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "My responsibility is for making fun of Bill Maher, or making fun of I suppose liberals for not reacting to Bill Maher, for saying this horrible thing about Dick Cheney.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "responsibility", "is", "for", "making", "fun", "of", "Bill", "Maher", ",", "or", "making", "fun", "of", "I", "suppose", "liberals", "for", "not", "reacting", "to", "Bill", "Maher", ",", "for", "saying", "this", "horrible", "thing", "about", "Dick", "Cheney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "Yeah?", "question_tokens": ["Yeah", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 744, "question": "What is the difference?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "The difference is if you read this in the full analytical context of where I wrote it, it was manifestly intended as a joke.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "difference", "is", "if", "you", "read", "this", "in", "the", "full", "analytical", "context", "of", "where", "I", "wrote", "it", ",", "it", "was", "manifestly", "intended", "as", "a", "joke", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 767, "question": "Where do you stand on abortion?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "stand", "on", "abortion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 768, "answer": "The same place I did when I ran for president last time around, which is I'm pro-life and proud to be so.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "same", "place", "I", "did", "when", "I", "ran", "for", "president", "last", "time", "around", ",", "which", "is", "I", "'m", "pro-life", "and", "proud", "to", "be", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "But you weren't always pro-life?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "were", "n't", "always", "pro-life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "That's correct.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ronald Reagan"]}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 780, "question": "How do you -- how do you counter that, given your view has changed so dramatically on that one issue?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "--", "how", "do", "you", "counter", "that", ",", "given", "your", "view", "has", "changed", "so", "dramatically", "on", "that", "one", "issue", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", ",", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 781, "answer": "Well, Ronald Reagan was also pro-choice and then became pro-life.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Ronald", "Reagan", "was", "also", "pro-choice", "and", "then", "became", "pro-life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CC", ":", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 787, "question": "On how many issues can you do it before you lose credibility?", "question_tokens": ["On", "how", "many", "issues", "can", "you", "do", "it", "before", "you", "lose", "credibility", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 788, "answer": "Well, the issue of great significance that everybody tells me I should just change my mind on and -- and do the politically expedient thing, which is to say that my health care plan was a terrible mistake, I'm not willing to do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "issue", "of", "great", "significance", "that", "everybody", "tells", "me", "I", "should", "just", "change", "my", "mind", "on", "and", "--", "and", "do", "the", "politically", "expedient", "thing", ",", "which", "is", "to", "say", "that", "my", "health", "care", "plan", "was", "a", "terrible", "mistake", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "willing", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", ":", "CC", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 789, "question": "Gay rights?", "question_tokens": ["Gay", "rights", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "I've always been in favor of preventing discrimination against people, whether they are homosexual or -- or straight...", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "always", "been", "in", "favor", "of", "preventing", "discrimination", "against", "people", ",", "whether", "they", "are", "homosexual", "or", "--", "or", "straight", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 805, "question": "Yes, but given that most gays would like the right now to legally get married in -- in many states, you are not in favor of all gay rights, are you?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "given", "that", "most", "gays", "would", "like", "the", "right", "now", "to", "legally", "get", "married", "in", "--", "in", "many", "states", ",", "you", "are", "not", "in", "favor", "of", "all", "gay", "rights", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 806, "answer": "And at the time when I ran for office, I made that very clear.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "at", "the", "time", "when", "I", "ran", "for", "office", ",", "I", "made", "that", "very", "clear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 813, "question": "Am I right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 814, "answer": "-- the gay community -- the gay community changed their perspective as to what they wanted.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "the", "gay", "community", "--", "the", "gay", "community", "changed", "their", "perspective", "as", "to", "what", "they", "wanted", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 821, "question": "What -- what is the gay rights that you're in favor of?", "question_tokens": ["What", "--", "what", "is", "the", "gay", "rights", "that", "you", "'re", "in", "favor", "of", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 822, "answer": "Well, equal rights in -- in employment, equal rights in -- I mean, for instance, as -- as the governor, I had members of my team that were gay.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "equal", "rights", "in", "--", "in", "employment", ",", "equal", "rights", "in", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "for", "instance", ",", "as", "--", "as", "the", "governor", ",", "I", "had", "members", "of", "my", "team", "that", "were", "gay", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP"], "qSentId": 825, "question": "Does your faith mean that you view homosexuality as a sin?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "your", "faith", "mean", "that", "you", "view", "homosexuality", "as", "a", "sin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 826, "answer": "You know, I -- I -- I still feel quite distinctly matters of personal faith from the leadership that one has in a -- in a political sense, I..", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "--", "I", "--", "I", "still", "feel", "quite", "distinctly", "matters", "of", "personal", "faith", "from", "the", "leadership", "that", "one", "has", "in", "a", "--", "in", "a", "political", "sense", ",", "I.."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 828, "question": "Can you do that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 829, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 831, "question": "Seriously?", "question_tokens": ["Seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 832, "answer": "You -- you don't begin to apply the doctrines of a religion to responsibility for -- for guiding a nation or for guiding a state.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "--", "you", "do", "n't", "begin", "to", "apply", "the", "doctrines", "of", "a", "religion", "to", "responsibility", "for", "--", "for", "guiding", "a", "nation", "or", "for", "guiding", "a", "state", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 833, "question": "What is the Mormon position on homosexuality being a sin?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "Mormon", "position", "on", "homosexuality", "being", "a", "sin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 834, "answer": "You know, that's something that you can take up with the church.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "something", "that", "you", "can", "take", "up", "with", "the", "church", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 847, "question": "Do you personally think homosexuality is a sin?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "personally", "think", "homosexuality", "is", "a", "sin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 848, "answer": "Nice try, but I'm not going to get into --", "answer_tokens": ["Nice", "try", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "get", "into", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 849, "question": "That's a valid question, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "valid", "question", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 850, "answer": "It's a valid question and my answer is nice try.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "valid", "question", "and", "my", "answer", "is", "nice", "try", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "TO", ":", "CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 852, "question": "Nice try at what?", "question_tokens": ["Nice", "try", "at", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 853, "answer": "I'm going to tell you that as a -- as a leader of the American people, I will do everything in my power to treat all people with respect and dignity and to -- and to advance the rights people have to choose their own course in life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "tell", "you", "that", "as", "a", "--", "as", "a", "leader", "of", "the", "American", "people", ",", "I", "will", "do", "everything", "in", "my", "power", "to", "treat", "all", "people", "with", "respect", "and", "dignity", "and", "to", "--", "and", "to", "advance", "the", "rights", "people", "have", "to", "choose", "their", "own", "course", "in", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "WP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 864, "question": "If you were made president, you wouldn't make any pronouncements whatsoever of a personal nature about any form of personal behavior?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "made", "president", ",", "you", "would", "n't", "make", "any", "pronouncements", "whatsoever", "of", "a", "personal", "nature", "about", "any", "form", "of", "personal", "behavior", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 865, "answer": "Well, I -- I'm not quite sure what -- what you're referring to...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "quite", "sure", "what", "--", "what", "you", "'re", "referring", "to", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", ":", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 888, "question": "Given that so many politicians, at the moment, are being hit by scandal, anything we don't know about Mitt?", "question_tokens": ["Given", "that", "so", "many", "politicians", ",", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "are", "being", "hit", "by", "scandal", ",", "anything", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "about", "Mitt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 889, "answer": "Well, you know, after 42 years of marriage, you know a person pretty -- pretty well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "after", "42", "years", "of", "marriage", ",", "you", "know", "a", "person", "pretty", "--", "pretty", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 892, "question": "Were you each other's first proper partners?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "each", "other", "'s", "first", "proper", "partners", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 893, "answer": "Well, for sure, I hope it was me, because --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "for", "sure", ",", "I", "hope", "it", "was", "me", ",", "because", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 899, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 900, "answer": "-- as a senior in high school.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "as", "a", "senior", "in", "high", "school", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 905, "question": "Would you like to elaborate on this?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "elaborate", "on", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 906, "answer": "He dated all of my girlfriends.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "dated", "all", "of", "my", "girlfriends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 908, "question": "Seriously?", "question_tokens": ["Seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 909, "answer": "I was extremely wary.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "extremely", "wary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 912, "question": "Don't I wish?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "I", "wish", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 913, "answer": "Now it -- now it's all coming out.", "answer_tokens": ["Now", "it", "--", "now", "it", "'s", "all", "coming", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 916, "question": "Have you ever drunk alcohol?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "drunk", "alcohol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 917, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 918, "question": "You don't -- you've never taken drugs?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "--", "you", "'ve", "never", "taken", "drugs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 919, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 921, "question": "And presumably, we never -- you never had an affair, because you couldn't have done it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "presumably", ",", "we", "never", "--", "you", "never", "had", "an", "affair", ",", "because", "you", "could", "n't", "have", "done", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 922, "answer": "Of course not.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 923, "question": "And you can say that with total non-Schwarzenegger certainty?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "can", "say", "that", "with", "total", "non-Schwarzenegger", "certainty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 924, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "JJR", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 929, "question": "So this is a -- I would say this is one of your trump cards, because when you look at all these politicians at the moment, whether it's Anthony Weiner or it's John Edwards or it's Arnold Schwarzenegger, the one thing we don't have to worry about in America if you're elected president is anything tumbling out of the -- the cupboard, right, Ann?", "question_tokens": ["So", "this", "is", "a", "--", "I", "would", "say", "this", "is", "one", "of", "your", "trump", "cards", ",", "because", "when", "you", "look", "at", "all", "these", "politicians", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "whether", "it", "'s", "Anthony", "Weiner", "or", "it", "'s", "John", "Edwards", "or", "it", "'s", "Arnold", "Schwarzenegger", ",", "the", "one", "thing", "we", "do", "n't", "have", "to", "worry", "about", "in", "America", "if", "you", "'re", "elected", "president", "is", "anything", "tumbling", "out", "of", "the", "--", "the", "cupboard", ",", "right", ",", "Ann", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 930, "answer": "It better not.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "better", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner", "John Edwards", "Arnold Schwarzenegger", "Ann"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 938, "question": "Well, you suffer from multiple sclerosis?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "suffer", "from", "multiple", "sclerosis", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 939, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 940, "question": "And you -- and you've also had to fight cancer?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "--", "and", "you", "'ve", "also", "had", "to", "fight", "cancer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 941, "answer": "And breast cancer, as well.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "breast", "cancer", ",", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 950, "question": "Would you -- would you go along with that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "--", "would", "you", "go", "along", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 951, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 953, "question": "He's a man of passion?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "a", "man", "of", "passion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 954, "answer": "Definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", ":", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 960, "question": "And, I mean, do you want to join in with Here, Mitt?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "want", "to", "join", "in", "with", "Here", ",", "Mitt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 961, "answer": "Well, my -- my sons, unfortunately, refer to something known as a Mitt-frontation.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "--", "my", "sons", ",", "unfortunately", ",", "refer", "to", "something", "known", "as", "a", "Mitt-frontation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 963, "question": "So you can lose your temper?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "can", "lose", "your", "temper", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 964, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJR", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 967, "question": "Quite explosive when he goes?", "question_tokens": ["Quite", "explosive", "when", "he", "goes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 968, "answer": "You know, I -- you know, I will say as both of us have gotten older, you certainly hope you mature.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "will", "say", "as", "both", "of", "us", "have", "gotten", "older", ",", "you", "certainly", "hope", "you", "mature", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ann"]}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 972, "question": "But what do they also call -- what do they call me?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "do", "they", "also", "call", "--", "what", "do", "they", "call", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 973, "answer": "Oh, Ann is the -- the Mitt stabilizer.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "Ann", "is", "the", "--", "the", "Mitt", "stabilizer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 986, "question": "That must worry you, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "must", "worry", "you", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 987, "answer": "It doesn't worry me.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "n't", "worry", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 993, "question": "And Governor, if -- if America managed to bring itself to vote for its first ever African-American president, do you believe that the mood now is right to potentially vote for its first Mormon president?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Governor", ",", "if", "--", "if", "America", "managed", "to", "bring", "itself", "to", "vote", "for", "its", "first", "ever", "African-American", "president", ",", "do", "you", "believe", "that", "the", "mood", "now", "is", "right", "to", "potentially", "vote", "for", "its", "first", "Mormon", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 994, "answer": "You know, I really don't think many people in this country make their vote based upon someone's religion.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "really", "do", "n't", "think", "many", "people", "in", "this", "country", "make", "their", "vote", "based", "upon", "someone", "'s", "religion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}]